Guide to the Dorothy Hayden Cudahy Papers AIA.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V. Commercial Recordings, 1916-1992, undated; 28.5 Linear Feet in 9 record cartons, 2 manuscript boxes, and 19 packing boxes
  - 45 rpm Recordings, 1916-1992; 1958-1988; 7.85 Linear Feet in 13 small LP boxes
    - Side A: Campbell, Jim, "Let's Share The Mornin'" Side B: Campbell, Jim, "Playin' The Lone Star Café", 1986 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 55)
    - Side A: Cahillane, Pat, "Dingle Bay" Side B: Cahillane, Pat, "Boys Of The Old Brigade", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 56)
    - Side A: Bagatelle, "Summer In Dublin" and "Leeson Street Lady" Side B: Bagatelle, "Is It Raining In Paris Tonight?" and "Second Violin", 1980, 1981, 1982 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 57)
    - Side A: Henry, Noel, "Old Flames" Side B: Henry, Noel, "Green Hills of Kerry", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 58)
    - Side A: Feeley, John, "The Lonesome Boatman" Side B: Feeley, John, "The Skyboat Song", 1987 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 59)
    - Side A: Melody, Martin, "Maggie" Side B: Melody, Martin, "The Ferryman (Pete St John)", 1986 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 60)
    - Side A: The Irish Balladeers, "The Bold Black And Tan" Side B: The Irish Balladeers, "The Orange, White And Green", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 61)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean, "Lonely Woods Of Upton" Side B: Dunphy, Sean, "Yellow Haired Woman", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 62)
    - Side A: MacNally, John, "Kathleen Mavourneen" and "The Star of the County Down" Side B: MacNally, John, "Macushla" and "The Old House", 1964 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 63)
    - Side A: Ball, Chris, "True Love Never Dies" Side B: Ball, Chris, "My Lovely Rose of Clare", 1984 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 64)
    - Side A: Kelly, Pete, "Wicklow Miners" and "Haste To The Wedding" Side B: Kelly, Pete, "The Morning Star" and "Green Meadows", 1984 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 65)
    - Side A: Brady, Sean, "The Thatcher Song" Side B: Brady, Sean, "Jewel of the Village", 1983 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 66)
    - Side A: O'Brien, Paddy, "Mayor Hannison's Fedora & Johnny Cronin's Fancy", "The Arragh Mountains & Father Burke's", and "Rigney's & Ambrose Moloney's" Side B: O'Brien, Paddy, "Youghal Quay & The Rambling Sailor", "The Munster Grass & The Banks of the Shannon", and "Captain Kelly's & The Rainy Day", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 67)
    - Side A: Logan, Al, "Barney Brannigan" Side B: Logan, Al, "Irish Pub Sing Along", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 68)
    - Side A: Coll, Brian, "These Are My Mountains" Side B: Coll, Brian, "Kentucky In The Morning", 1971 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 69)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "Don't Bother To Knock (Riley's Brew)" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "Little Town In Old County Down", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 70)
    - Side A: The Celtic Flavour Band, "Sweet Sixteen" Side B: The Celtic Flavour Band, "The Candy Store On The Corner", 1984 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 71)
    - Side A: Kelly, Pete, "Wicklow Miners" and "Haste To The Wedding" Side B: Kelly, Pete, "The Morning Star" and "Green Meadows", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 72)
    - Side A: Vaughan, Martin, "Kitty Machree" Side B: Tulla Ceili Band, "Pinch of Snuff", 1974 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 73)
    - Side A: Pickering, Johnny, "Bird In The Bush", "Maid of Mt. Kisco", and "Turkey In The Straw" Side B: Pickering, Johnny, "McCormick's Fancy", "Rose In The Heather", and "Jeff's Pal", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 1)
    - Side A: The Tritones, "The Spinning Wheel" Side B: The Tritones, "Nineteen Sixteen", 1968 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 2)
    - Side A: The Alexander Brothers, "Remember The Children" Side B: The Alexander Brothers, "Coulter's Candy", 1968 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 3)
    - Side A: Maguire, Sean, "Walls of Limerick", "Petronella", "London Lassies", and "Devil Among The Tailors" Side B: Maguire, Sean, "Idle Road" and "Kings Favorite", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 4)
    - Side A: Rebel Irish Women, "Helena Moloney", "Kathleen Behan", and "Maud Gonne MacBride" Side B: Rebel Irish Women, "Helena Moloney", 1966 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 5)
    - Cunningham, Larry, undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 6)
    - Side A: Gallagher, Bridie, "Lovely Derry On The Banks Of The Foyle" and "Cottage By The Lee" Side B: Gallagher, Bridie, "Homes Of Donegal" and "That Tumble-Down Shack In Athlone", 1960 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 7)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean, "The Johnny Thompson Song" and "Flower Of Macroom" Side B: Dunphy, Sean, "Danny Boy" and "Black and Tan Gun", 1966 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 8)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean, "Christmas Polka" Side B: Dunphy, Sean, "She's Mine", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 9)
    - Side A: "Slip Jig" Side B: "Madame Bonaparte" and "Three Sea Captains", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 10)
    - Side A: Donaghy, Eileen, "Cork" and "The Humour Is On Me Now" Side B: Donaghy, Eileen, "The Auld Plaid Shawl" and "Rathfriland On The Hill", 1959 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 11)
    - Side A: Grabeau, Bob, "Where Shannon Waters Flow", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 12)
    - Side A: The Millionaires, "The Merry Ploughboy" Side B: The Millionaires, "The Sea Around Us", 1966 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 13)
    - Side A: McCusker Brothers, "Copperplate", "Tar Bolton", and "Maid Behind The Bar" Side B: McCusker Brothers, "Newtown Fancy", "Donnybrook Fair", and "Knights of St. Patrick", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 14)
    - Side A: The Gingerman, "Ha - Penny Bridge" Side B: The Gingerman, "The Alamo", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 15)
    - Side A: Cribben, Shea, "Give Your Love A Chance" Side B: Cribben, Shea, "What About The Last Time", 1968 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 16)
    - Side A: McCann, Jim, "The Tumble-Down Shack In Athlone" Side B: McCann, Jim, "When You're Winging Your Way To Old Ireland", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 17)
    - Side A: The Gallowglass Ceili Band, "Hornpipe" and "Irish March" Side B: The Gallowglass Ceili Band, "Military Two-Step" and "Set Dance", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 18)
    - Side A: The Gentiles, "Marlene" Side B: The Gentiles, "Goodbye Baby", 1968 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 19)
    - Side A: Flynn, Martin, "The Irish Rover" Side B: Flynn, Martin, "Oh To Be In Donaree", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 20)
    - Side A: The Go Lucky Four, "Show Me A Man (Who Doesn't Love The Land Where He Was Born)" Side B: The Go Lucky Four, "Isn't It Grand Boys", 1966 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 21)
    - Side A: Kings Showband, "Beautiful Dreamer" Side B: Kings Showband, "I Fall To Pieces", 1966 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 22)
    - Side A: Connolly, Mary, "Heaven Around Galway Bay" Side B: Connolly, Mary, "In The Corner Of My Prison Cell", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 23)
    - Side A: O'Donnell, Eugene, "Kilkenny Races" and "Madame Bonaparte" Side B: O'Donnell, Eugene, "The Hurling Boys" and "Three Sea Captains", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 24)
    - Side A: McGonigle, Mary, "My Hometown In Co. Mayo" Side B: McGonigle Mary, "Farewell to the Green Hills of Erin", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 25)
    - Side A: Flynn, Joe, "The Broken Hearted Farmer" Side B: Flynn, Joe, "The Old Bog Road", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 26)
    - Side A: Daly, Pat and Noonan, Paddy, "Irish Soldier Laddie", "Reels: Mason's Apron, Donegal, Peter St.", "Northern Lights of Old Aberdeen" Side B: Daly, Pat, and Noonan, Paddy, "Whisling Rufus", "Patriot Game", and "Highland Polkas", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 27)
    - Side A: Gill, Earl, "Sunset" Side B: Gill, Earl, "If I Could Choose", 1967 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 28)
    - Side A: O'Duffy, Michael, "O'Donnell Abu" Side B: O'Duffy, Michael, "Slattery's Mounted Fut", 1967 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 29)
    - Side A: Brady, Willie, "Boys From The Co. Mayo" Side B: Brady, Willie, "The Whistling Gypsy", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 30)
    - Side A: Devine, Owen, "Mrs. Murphy's Chowder" and "Eileen O'Grady" Side B: Devine, Owen, "With my shillelagh under my arm" and "By the light of the moon", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 31)
    - Side A: McCann, Jim, "The Rocky Road To Dublin" and "Little Town In The Old County Down", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 32)
    - Side A: Donaghy, Eileen, "The Old Water Mill" and "Wee Cup Of Tay" Side B: Donaghy, Eileen, "McCarthy's Party" and "Sittin' On The Bridge Below The Town", 1960 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 33)
    - Side A: The Clancy Brothers, "Beer, Beer, Beer" Side B: The Clancy Brothers, "Jennifer Gentle", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 34)
    - Side A: McParland, Tommy, "Dungarvan My Hometown" Side B: McParland, Tommy, "Rathfriland On The Hill", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 35)
    - Side A: The Go Lucky Four, "Up Went Nelson" Side B: The Go Lucky Four, "Off To Dublin In The Green", 1966 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 36)
    - Side A: Miller, Mitch, "Hinky Dinky Parlez-Vous", "She'll Be Comin' Round the Mountain", "Polly Wolly Doodle", "Wait for the Wagon", "The Old Grey Mare" Side B: Miller, Mitch, "Our Boys Will Shine Tonight", "Give My Regards to Broadway", "Under the Bamboo Tree", "Bill Bailey", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 37)
    - Side A: Macleod, Jim, "March of the Penny Whistler" Side B: Macleod, Jim, "The Happy Whistler", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 38)
    - Side A: Flaherty, Connie, "My Last Wish" Side B: Carrig, Johnny, "The Ballad of Lord Nelson", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 39)
    - Side A: Sheehan, Eileen, "Ballyseedy Cross" and "You'll be lonely Little Sweetheart in the Spring" Side B: Sheehan, Eileen, "The Golden Jubilee" and "Whistling Phil McHugh", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 40)
    - Side A: Donaghy, Eileen, "Six Mile Song" and "Boys of Coleraine" Side B: Donaghy, Eileen, "The Irish Rover" and "The Irish Fire Brigade", 1960 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 41)
    - Side A: Gill, Frank, "You'll Come Again To Castlebar" Side B: Gill, Frank, "Singing The Blues", 1968 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 42)
    - Side A: O'Kelly, Betty, "Goodbye, Johnny Dear" Side B: O'Kelly, Betty, "The Homes of Donegal", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 43)
    - Side A: Dana, "All Kinds of Everything" Side B: Dana, "Channel Breeze", 1970 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 44)
    - Side A: Flynn, Martin, "The Last Farewell" Side B: Flynn, Martin, "The Town I Love So Well", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 45)
    - Side A: Shand, Jimmy, "Loch Lomond", "I belong to Glasgow", and "My Bonnie lies over the Ocean" Side B: Shand, Jimmy, "Roamin' in the gloamin'", "I love a Lassie", "Stop your tickling Jock", and "Just a wee deoch and doris", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 46)
    - Side A: Kennedy, Calum, "The Scottish Working Man" Side B: Kennedy, Calum, "The Dark Island", 1967 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 47)
    - Side A: Mahon, Joe, "The Star of Logy Bay" Side B: Mahon, Joe, "Dear Old Donegal", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 48)
    - Side A: Keeling, Tony, "Crystal Chandelier" Side B: Keeling, Tony, "City Lights", 1967 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 49)
    - Side A: McGonigle, Mary, "My Old Home in Mayo" Side B: McGonigle Mary, "Irelands 32", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 50)
    - Side A: Rotton Spuds, "I'll Take You Home Kathleen" Side B: Rotton Spuds, "Glocca Morra", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 51)
    - Side A: Lee, Anne Patricia, "Cottage By The Lee" Side B: Lee, Anne Patricia, "Home To Mayo", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 52)
    - Side A: Kingston, Noel, "Glorious Green" Side B: Noonan, Paddy, "Irish Coffee", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 53)
    - Side A: Flynn, Martin, "Oh To Be In Donaree" Side B: Flynn, Martin, "The Irish Rover", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 54)
    - Side A: McGee, Charlie, "Thank God for John F. Kennedy" and "The Roads of Donegal" Side B: McGee, Charlie, "Ballad of Johnny Doran" and "City Named Derry", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 55)
    - Side A: McEvoy, John, "Muirsheen Durkin" Side B: McEvoy, John, "Those Brown Eyes", 1966 (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 56)
    - Side A: O'Kelly, Betty, "Connemara Shore" Side B: O'Kelly, Betty, "The Green Glens of Antrim", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 57)
    - Side A: Margo, "The Girl From Donegal" Side B: Margo, "Happy Birthday Me", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 58)
    - Side A: Graye, Tony, "D.J. Blues" Side B: Graye, Tony, "Both Feet on the Move", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 59)
    - Side A: The Moonshiners, "Minglay" Side B: The Moonshiners, "The Moonshiner", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 60)
    - Side A: Shand, Jimmy, "Harvest Home" and "Trumpet Hornpipe" Side B: Shand, Jimmy, "Pet o' the Pipers", "Father O'Flynn", and "Sorry to part", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 61)
    - Side A: Pickering, Johnny, "Bird In The Bush", "Maid of Mt. Kisco", and "Turkey In The Straw" Side B: Pickering, Johnny, "McCormick's Fancy", "Rose In The Heather", and "Jeff's Pal", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 62)
    - Side A: Lee, Frank, "Hornpipes Medley" and "Irish Jigs Medley" Side B: Lee, Frank, "I'm 94 To-Day" and "Ye Can Come And See The Baby", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 63)
    - Side A: Ryan, Sean, "Kevin Barry" and "The Lake Near Killaloe" Side B: Ryan, Sean, "The Old Bog Road" and "When you and I were young, Maggie", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 64)
    - Side A: Noonan, Paddy, "Love's Young Dream", "The Moon Behind The Hill", and "The Castle of Dromore" Side B: Noonan, Paddy, "The Bridge of Athlone" and "Smash The Window", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 65)
    - Side A: Glenside Ceilidhe Band, "Smash The Windows", "The Bugler's Frolic", "Off She Goes", and "Skipping To School" Side B: Glenside Ceilidhe Band, "Hay In The Barn", "Merry Reapers", and "Boys of Blue Hill", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 66)
    - Side A: O'Donnell, Eugene, "Garden of Daisies" and "The Hunt" Side B: O'Donnell, Eugene, "Jockey at the Fair" and "Planxty Drury", undated (Box 82, Sound disc--vinyl 67)
    - Side A: O'Neill, James, "Pub With No Beer" Side B: O'Neill, James, "When Peggy O'Dea Came To Mullinalee", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 1)
    - Side A: Rempell, Bill, "Back To Donegal" Side B: Rempell, Bill, "The Men Of The West", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 2)
    - Side A: Rempell, Bill, "Back To Donegal" Side B: Rempell, Bill, "The Men Of The West", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 3)
    - Side A: Donaghy, Eileen, "Faughan Side" and "Little Old Mud Cabin (In The Hills)" Side B: Donaghy, Eileen, "The Bard of Armagh" and "Blue Hills of Antrim", 1959 (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 4)
    - Side A: McCauley, Johnny, "The Pretty Girl From Omagh" Side B: McCauley, Johnny, "Just Pretendin'", 1968 (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 5)
    - Side A: Brady, Willie, "Boys From The Co. Mayo" Side B: Brady, Willie, "The Whistling Gypsy", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 6)
    - Side A: Greehy, Anne, "Peg Of My Heart" Side B: Greehy, Anne, "Paddy", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 7)
    - Side A: Gregory & The Cadets, "Angeline" Side B: Gregory & The Cadets, "C'mon Marianne", 1968 (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 8)
    - Side A: Greehy, Anne, "The Boys From Co. Armagh" Side B: Greehy, Anne, "I'll Remember You Love In My Prayers", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 9)
    - Side A: The McNulty Family, "Homes of Donegal" Side B: The McNulty Family, "Boys From The County Armagh", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 10)
    - Side A: Jordan, Tony, "Long Black Hair Of Bonny" Side B: Jordan, Tony, "The Wind Calls", 1967 (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 11)
    - Side A: Kennedy, Calum, "The Scottish Working Man" Side B: Kennedy, Calum, "The Dark Island", 1967 (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 12)
    - Side A: Duggan, Don, "Let Her Dance" Side B: Duggan, Don, "Westmeath Bachelor", 1968 (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 13)
    - Side A: Donaghy, Eileen, "With My Shillelagh Under My Arm" Side B: Donaghy, Eileen, "Phil The Fluter's Ball", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 14)
    - Side A: Derrane, Joe, "The Union Reel", "Harvest Home Hornpipe", and "The Bird In The Tree Hornpipe" Side B: Derrane, Joe, "The Merry Blacksmith Reel", "The Limestone Rock Reel", "The Fisherman's Widow Jig", and "Devine's Favorite Jig", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 15)
    - Side A: Greehy, Anne, "The Irish Patrol" Side B: Greehy, Anne, "Wrap The Green Flag Round Me", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 16)
    - Side A: Dolan, Joe, "Workday Blues" Side B: Dolan, Joe, "The House With The Whitewashed Gable", 1967 (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 17)
    - Side A: O'Donnell, Eugene, "The Blackbird" and "The Piper" Side B: O'Donnell, Eugene, "Hurry The Jug", "Humors of Bandon", and "The Orange Rogue", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 18)
    - Side A: Gill, Frank, "You'll Come Again To Castlebar" Side B: Gill, Frank, "Singing The Blues", 1968 (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 19)
    - Side A: Floody, Pat, "Reels & Jigs" Side B: Cournane, Bart, "Rocks of Bawn" and "Gentle Mother", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 20)
    - Side A: McParland, Tommy, "Dungarvan My Hometown" Side B: McParland, Tommy, "Rathfriland On The Hill", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 21)
    - Side A: McCormack, John, "Come Back to Erin" and "Killarney" Side B: McCormack, John, "Savoureen Deelish" and "Kathleen Mavourneen", 1963 (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 22)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean, "Lonely Woods of Upton" Side B: Dunphy, Sean, "Yellow Haired Woman", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 23)
    - Side A: Big Johnny, "Biddy Reilly" Side B: Big Johnny, "Tippy Toeing", 1967 (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 24)
    - Side A: The Gingerman, "Ha - Penny Bridge" Side B: The Gingerman, "The Alamo", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 25)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "There's A Little Bit Of Irish (In Everybody's Heart)" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "Let Him Go, Let Him Tarry", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 26)
    - Side A: Brady, Willie, "Sean South Of Garryowen" Side B: Brady, Willie, "Johnson's Motor Car", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 27)
    - Side A: Owens, Jesse, "Tipperary Daisy" Side B: Owens, Jesse, "Peggy Gordon", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 28)
    - Side A: Greehy, Anne, "The Forty Shades Of Green" Side B: Greehy, Anne, "How Are Things In Glocca Morra", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 29)
    - Side A: Daly, Pat, and Noonan, Paddy, "Irish Soldier Laddie", "Reels", and "Northern Lights of Old Aberdeen" Side B: Daly, Pat, and Noonan, Paddy, "Whisling Rufus", "Patriot Game", and "Highland Polkas", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 30)
    - Side A: Lynch, Pat, "The Irish Soldier" Side B: Lynch, Pat, "Big Job", 1967 (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 31)
    - Side A: Flynn, Martin, "The Last Farewell" Side B: Flynn, Martin, "The Town I Love So Well", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 32)
    - Side A: Donohue, Gabriel, "Land Of A Thousand Welcomes" Side B: Donohue, Gabriel, "Only The Rivers Run Free", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 33)
    - Side A: Daly, Pat, and Noonan, Paddy, "Irish Soldier Laddie", "Reels", and "Northern Lights of Old Aberdeen" Side B: Daly, Pat, and Noonan, Paddy, "Whisling Rufus", "Patriot Game", and "Highland Polkas", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 34)
    - Side A: Cassidy, Mike, "Bernadette In Command" Side B: The Vigilantes, "Fleath at Bogside", 1969 (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 35)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "Mick McGilligan's Ball" and "If I Were A Blackbird" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "Isle of Innisfree" and "Doonaree", undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 36)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean, "The Johnny Thompson Song" and "Flower of Macroom" Side B: Dunphy, Sean, "Danny Boy" and "Black and Tan Gun", 1966 (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 37)
    - Side A: Donaghy, Eileen, "Six Mile Song" and "Boys of Coleraine" Side B: Donaghy, Eileen, "The Irish Rover" and "The Irish Fire Brigade" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 38)
    - Side A: The Tinkers, "Tell Ireland…" Side B: The Tinkers, "The Rising Of The Moon" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 39)
    - Side A: Miller, Maureen, "The Moon Behind The Hill" and "Sliabh Na Mban" Side B: Miller, Maureen, "An Chuilfhionn" and "The Castle Of Dromore" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 40)
    - Side A: Donaghy, Eileen, "Trottin' To The Fair" and "Song of the Backwoods" Side B: Donaghy, Eileen, "Ballyshannon" and "My Lagan Love" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 41)
    - (empty sleeve), undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 42)
    - Dunphy, Sean, "Lonely Woods Of Upton" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 43)
    - (empty sleeve), undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 44)
    - Side A: Gallowglass Ceili Band, "Siege of Ennis" and "Irish Old Time Waltz" Side B: Gallowglass Ceili Band, "Military Two Step" and "Harvest Time Jig" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 45)
    - Ryan, Kevin (empty sleeve), undated (Box 83, Sound disc--vinyl 46)
    - Side A: McCarthy, Sean, "Your Land" Side B: McCarthy, Sean, "New Land", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 1)
    - Side A: Gallagher, Bridie, "The Turfman From Ardee" Side B: Gallagher, Bridie, "Destination Donegal", 1967 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 2)
    - Side A: Grabeau, Bob, "An Irish Blessing" Side B: Grabeau, Bob, "Where Shannon Waters Flow", 1978 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 3)
    - Side A: Treacy, "Murphy's Volunteers" Side B: Treacy, "Red Haired Mary", 1968 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 4)
    - Side A: Byrne, Mike, "My Jersey Irish Girl" Side B: Byrne, Mike, "Four Green Fields", 1986 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 5)
    - Side A: Henry, Noel, "Mr. Bojangles" Side B: Henry, Noel, "There's Whiskey In The Jar", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 6)
    - Side A: The Hoedowners, "True Love's A Blessing" Side B: The Hoedowners, "Showball Crazy", 1966 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 7)
    - Side A: Darcel, Denise, "Father O'Conner" Side B: Darcel, Denise, "Father O'Conner", 1976 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 8)
    - Side A: Makem, Tommy, "Winds Are Singing Freedom" Side B: Makem, Tommy, "Lord Of The Dance", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 9)
    - Side A: Melody, Martin, "Maggie" Side B: Melody, Martin, "The Ferryman (Pete St John)", 1986 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 10)
    - Side A: Nolan and Birmingham, "Cavan Girl" Side B: Nolan and Birmingham, "Mary From Dungloe", 1988 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 11)
    - Side A: Kenny, Tony, "Pretty Paper" Side B: Kenny, Tony, "Any Dream Will Do", 1985 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 12)
    - Side A: Shand, Jimmy, "Scotland The Brave", "Uist Tramping Song", and "We're no awa' tae bide awa'" Side B: Shand, Jimmy, "A Guid New Year" and "Auld Lang Syne", 1957 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 13)
    - Side A: Furey Brothers, "When You Were Sweet Sixteen" Side B: Furey Brothers, "Big Ships A'Sailing", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 14)
    - Side A: Brady, Sean, "The Ballad Of Red Ken" Side B: Brady, Sean, "The Derry Bogside", 1984 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 15)
    - Side A: Brady, Sean, "The Garret Song" Side B: Brady, Sean, "No Place Like Home", 1985 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 16)
    - Side A: Moran, Joey, "Flight of Earls" Side B: Moran, Joey, "Pat Murphy's Meadow", 1988 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 17)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "Wonderful World Of My Dreams" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "The Worst Mistake", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 18)
    - Side A: Flynn, Martin, "Galway Shawl" Side B: Flynn, Martin, "Four Green Fields", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 19)
    - Side A: Moore, Christy, "The Ballad Of Ballinamore" Side B: Moore, Christy, "Hey, Ronnie Reagan", 1984 (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 20)
    - Side A: Murphy, John, "The Lark" Side B: Murphy, John, "Galway Girl", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 21)
    - Side A: Reilly, Paddy, "Flight Of Earls" and "O'Connell's Steam Engine" Side B: Reilly, Paddy, "Sally Gardens", undated (Box 84, Sound disc--vinyl 22)